<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on St John&#39;s Church, Walton, Chesterfield</title>
    <link>https://stjohnswalton.co.uk/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on St John&#39;s Church, Walton, Chesterfield</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>St John&#39;s Church, Walton {year}.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 12:33:57 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://stjohnswalton.co.uk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Worship</title>
      <link>https://stjohnswalton.co.uk/worship/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 09:40:15 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stjohnswalton.co.uk/worship/</guid>
      <description>Sundays Morning 9:00 am This service follows the traditional pattern of Holy Communion, with hymns from Songs of Fellowship, and is followed by morning coffee in the Church Centre afterwards. Whether you are a regular communicant or simply enjoy a traditional experience of worship, you will be very warmly welcome to join us.
Morning 10:45 am With a varied pattern of worship across the month, 1045 is characterised by a relaxed approach and a mixture of sung worship led by the band, with liturgy and song words and media projected on both sides of the church.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ministries</title>
      <link>https://stjohnswalton.co.uk/ministries/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 11:13:55 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stjohnswalton.co.uk/ministries/</guid>
      <description>Alpha Course Alpha is a series of sessions over ten weeks that give people a great opportunity to explore what Christians believe in a relaxed, informal setting.
We look at key themes of Christian faith, such as who Jesus is, why he died on the Cross, what faith is, and why it’s important. We also explore those dimensions of Christian faith that connect directly with our personal experiences of life, such as suffering, money and possessions, sin, temptation and addictions, and thinking about how we can make the most of our lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://stjohnswalton.co.uk/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 13:14:29 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stjohnswalton.co.uk/about/</guid>
      <description>Clergy Vicar: Rev&amp;rsquo;d Nick Green CA
Curate: Rev&amp;rsquo;d Jo Harbridge
Rev&amp;rsquo;d Royston Smith SSM - Self-supporting minister
Rev&amp;rsquo;d Julie Stanton NSM - Non-stipendiary minister</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Safeguarding</title>
      <link>https://stjohnswalton.co.uk/safeguarding/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 13:35:08 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stjohnswalton.co.uk/safeguarding/</guid>
      <description>Who to contact St John&amp;rsquo;s Church takes our duty of care for the Safeguarding of children, young people and vulnerable adults seriously. If you have any concerns please email in confidence to safeguardingchildren@stjohnswalton.co.uk, or safeguardingadults@stjohnswalton.co.uk
Our policy St John&amp;rsquo;s Church Council takes its duty of care for children, young people and vulnerable adults attending worship or other activities at church seriously.
St John’s is subject to the Derby Diocese Safeguarding Children and Young People Policies and Procedures, and works closely with the diocese to ensure good practice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weddings</title>
      <link>https://stjohnswalton.co.uk/weddings/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 13:35:08 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stjohnswalton.co.uk/weddings/</guid>
      <description>Weddings To enquire about having your wedding at St John&#39;s please fill in and submit the form below.
NB: please scroll down to complete the form.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baptism</title>
      <link>https://stjohnswalton.co.uk/baptism/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 14:16:32 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stjohnswalton.co.uk/baptism/</guid>
      <description>Please fill in the baptism enquire from below. NB: please scroll down to complete the form.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join us</title>
      <link>https://stjohnswalton.co.uk/join/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 14:16:32 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stjohnswalton.co.uk/join/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
