<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on St John&#39;s Church, Walton, Chesterfield</title>
    <link>https://stjohnswalton.co.uk/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on St John&#39;s Church, Walton, Chesterfield</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>St John&#39;s Church, Walton {year}.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 12:33:57 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://stjohnswalton.co.uk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Worship</title>
      <link>https://stjohnswalton.co.uk/worship/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 09:40:15 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stjohnswalton.co.uk/worship/</guid>
      <description>Sundays Morning 9:00 am This service follows the traditional pattern of Holy Communion, with hymns from Songs of Fellowship.
Morning 10:45 am Worship, led by the band, with liturgy and song words projected so they are easily followed.
Evening 8:00 pm Just Be is a gentle time of worship, prayer, reflection and mutual encouragement.
Tuesdays Evening 11:00 am Tuesday Worship is more than simply a time of worship together; from the beginning, friendship with Jesus has been an experience of community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Events</title>
      <link>https://stjohnswalton.co.uk/events/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 11:13:35 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stjohnswalton.co.uk/events/</guid>
      <description># Google calendar inserted with shortcode</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ministries</title>
      <link>https://stjohnswalton.co.uk/ministries/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 11:13:55 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stjohnswalton.co.uk/ministries/</guid>
      <description>Baptism Baptism is the gateway to life in Christ and becoming a member of the Church. If you ever visit an ancient church, this is why you&amp;rsquo;ll always find the font at the back of the church near the door.
If you would like to know more about Baptism for your child, please complete the Baptism enquiry form We will put you in touch with a member of the Baptism Team who will meet with you, give you all the information you need and support you as explore this journey of faith.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://stjohnswalton.co.uk/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 13:14:29 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stjohnswalton.co.uk/about/</guid>
      <description>Clergy Vicar: Rev&amp;rsquo;d Nick Green CA
Curate: Rev&amp;rsquo;d Jo Harbridge
Rev&amp;rsquo;d Royston Smith SSM - Self-supporting minister
Rev&amp;rsquo;d Julie Stanton NSM - Non-stipendiary minister</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bereavement</title>
      <link>https://stjohnswalton.co.uk/bereavement/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 13:50:54 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stjohnswalton.co.uk/bereavement/</guid>
      <description>The death of someone we love can be one of the most stressful and devastating events of our lives. It is a shocking and bewildering experience and not something to be ‘got over’ in a matter of weeks or months.
St John’s offers support through this difficult time, helping and enabling the saying of goodbyes, and walking alongside people as they begin to live with their loss.
We have ministers available to lead funeral services either at St John’s or at the Crematorium.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Safeguarding</title>
      <link>https://stjohnswalton.co.uk/safeguarding/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 13:35:08 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stjohnswalton.co.uk/safeguarding/</guid>
      <description>Who to contact St John&amp;rsquo;s Church takes our duty of care for the Safeguarding of children, young people and vulnerable adults seriously. If you have any concerns please email in confidence to safeguardingchildren@stjohnswalton.co.uk, or safeguardingadults@stjohnswalton.co.uk
Our policy St John&amp;rsquo;s Church Council takes its duty of care for children, young people and vulnerable adults attending worship or other activities at church seriously.
St John’s is subject to the Derby Diocese Safeguarding Children and Young People Policies and Procedures, and works closely with the diocese to ensure good practice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weddings</title>
      <link>https://stjohnswalton.co.uk/weddings/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 13:35:08 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stjohnswalton.co.uk/weddings/</guid>
      <description>Weddings To enquire about having your wedding at St John&#39;s please fill in and submit the form below.
NB: please scroll down to complete the form.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Connect</title>
      <link>https://stjohnswalton.co.uk/connect/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 13:14:19 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stjohnswalton.co.uk/connect/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baptism</title>
      <link>https://stjohnswalton.co.uk/baptism/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 14:16:32 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stjohnswalton.co.uk/baptism/</guid>
      <description>Please fill in the baptism enquire from below. NB: please scroll down to complete the form.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://stjohnswalton.co.uk/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 11:14:07 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stjohnswalton.co.uk/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
